<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Scuffle's Stuff: A Game-Breaking Cheat Mod</name>
	<author>Scuffle Kerfuffle</author>
	<targetVersion>0.18.0</targetVersion>
	<description>
	  [h1]Scuffle's Stuff: A Game-Breaking Cheat Mod[/h1]

	  [b]Current Version[/b]
	  [b]0.0.1 Alpha[/b]

	  [b]Target RimWorld Version[/b]
	  0.18.0 Beta

	  [b]Credits[/b]
	  Inspiration (but currently not code) drawn from the following mods:
	  [list]
	  [*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=729690064]Feed The Colonists[/url]
	  [*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=973091113]Climate Control[/url]
	  [*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1242508171]Mending Beds[/url]
	  [/list]
	  Items pulled from the following mods:
	  [list]
	  [*][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1205024704]Modular Tables[/url] by [url=http://steamcommunity.com/id/kaptain_kavern]kaptain_kavern[/url]
	  [*][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=722085442]ED-Embrasures[/url] by [url=http://steamcommunity.com/id/jaxxa]Jaxxa[/url]
	  [*][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=710101929]Ed-CheatReactor[/url] by [url=http://steamcommunity.com/id/jaxxa]Jaxxa[/url]
	  [/list]

	  [b]Contributors (not including credited mods above)[/b]
	  Scuffle Kerfuffle

	  [b]Description[/b]
	  Are you tired of mining massive amounts of gold for beautiful beds? Want your Pawns to be happy but for your colony to still show as super poor so those pesky raiders won't care about you (as much)? Do you want turrets that hit harder than a muffalo's charge? How about walls and embrasures that are stronger than the smell of rotten eggs?

	  If you said yes to any of these things you are a dirty, dirty cheater. But then again: so am I! This mod adds a slew of things I wanted to see. None of them are balanced. They are, in fact, very likely to ruin the game for you if you use them. These things are just stupidly overpowered. You have been warned.

	  [b]Notes[/b]
	  [list]
	  [*]I am not an artist. I'm awful at making things look pretty. That being the case, everything below uses some vanilla visual or other. If you'd like to make something prettier, please feel free to do so and send it over. I'll happily include it and give you an artist's credit.
	  [*]All items have a base market value of 0.05, a "stuff" cost of 1, and a work cost of 1.
	  [*]Base-Related items (walls, furniture, floors, etc.) have a beauty value of 5000 in addition to their other stats. Differences are marked with [i]emphasis[/i].
	  [*]Apparel items provide perfect insulation and cooling. They are designed to completely offset the worst temperatures.
	  [*]Plants intended for Pawns can be grown via hydroponics.
	  [*]All plants have an ideal temperature range of -50f to 140f.
	  [*]All ranged weapons and turrets have a base accuracy of 100% at all ranges.
	  [*][b]I have not tested compatibility with any other mods whatsoever. Caveat Emptor![/b]
	  [*]This mod is licensed under the MIT License (3.0).
	  [*]Source can be found on [url=https://www.github.com/ScuffleKerfuffle/RimWorld]My GitHub[/url]
	  [/list]

	  [b]Included in this Mod[/b]

	  [b]Apparel[/b]

	  [list]
	  [*]Hyper Armor - A suit of power armor with 120% resistance to all damage types.
	  [*]Hyper Armor Helm - A suit of power armor with 120% resistance to all damage types.
	  [/list]

	  [b]Climate Control[/b]

	  [list]
	  [*]TempurMatic 5000 - A 1x1 climate control device that can set temperatures from -50f to 120f. Consumes no power, has no exhaust, and is powerful enough to control a 20x20 room (I think).
	  [/list]

	  [b]Farming[/b]

	  [list]
	  [*]HyperHay (I'm lazy with naming) - A hay that cannot be harvested, but that provides 2 nutrition when eaten by animals that eat plants. Grows in a half day.
	  [*]NutriShroom - A mushroom that is a meat substitute and provides 2 nutrition. Grows in a half day. Great for use with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=729690064]Feed the Colonists[/url].
	  [*]NutriBerry - A berry that provides 2 nutrition. Grows in a half day.
	  [/list]

	  [b]Furniture[/b]

	  [list]
	  [*]Comfort Chair 5000 - An armchair with base comfort of 2.0.
	  [*]Comfort Bed 5000 - A bed with base comfort of 2.0.
	  [*]ImpressoMatic Dining Table - A modular dining table with [i]beauty 10000[/i].
	  [*]Comfort Dining Chair 5000 - A dining chair with base comfort of 2.0.
	  [/list]

	  [b]Power[/b]

	  [list]
	  [*]GenaTron 5000 - A 1x1 power source that generates 500,000 power.
	  [/list]

	  [b]Security[/b]

	  [list]
	  [*]Hyper Turret - A 1x1 turret that has an extended range. It should be non-lethal.
	  [/list]

	  [b]Structure[/b]

	  [list]
	  [*]ImpregnaWall - A wall with 150,000 hit points. If your pawns die behind these walls, it's because death came from within.
	  [*]ImpregnaWall Embrasure Edition - An embrasure with, you guessed it, 150,000 hit points.
	  [*]ImpregnaDoor - A door with 150,000 hit points.
	  [*]Auto ImpregnaDoor - An auto-door with 150,000 hit points.
	  [/list]

	  [b]Weapons[/b]

	  [list]
	  [*]Shock Rifle - A rifle based on the charged rifle that deals heavy consciousness damage.
	  [*]Phase Rifle - A rifle based on the charged rifle that deals heavy damage.
	  [*]Skull Crusher - A mace that deals heavy blunt damage. Lives up to its name.
	  [/list]

	  [b]Possible Future Functionality[/b]

	  [list]
	  [*]Make the bed a mending bed similar to [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1242508171]Mending Beds[/url], but with the ridiculous values of the other furniture.
	  [*]Make the cooler wall-mounted like the vents from [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=973091113]Climate Control[/url].
	  [*]Give the turret two firing modes or add a lethal version.
	  [/list]
  </description>
</ModMetaData>